To Whom It May Concern,

Throughout my life, I've never stopped listening to music. It's the only medium that I consume for hours a day. Run For Cover has been a mainstay. My first introduction being through Daniel Bressette, the designer of Transit's Keep This To Yourself; since then I've been following along.

I started learning about Graphic Design when I was nine years old, I learned about Graphic Design through programs like Adobe's late Fireworks. Later learning the rest of the Adobe Suite through means of designing whatever I could, mock album covers, internet forum signatures, etc. I'm currently studying at the Maryland Institute College of Art where I entered as a Graphic Design major, and going into my Junior year I decided to change my major to Photography to broaden my horizons, and round out my ability with Graphic Design.

After years of listening, it was when Tuesdays with Tay started that I realized that RFC was something special. I didn't know that a show could mean so much to me, and I would show how much it meant with the Tuesdays with Tay Archive. This project is why I'm the one for RFC, I have shown my dedication for the label and the people behind it.

As someone who has recorded his own music and currently works with live bands, I understand the connection between the artist, the label, and their craft. An example being album art is beyond just a pretty picture, it's apart of the work.

Now that I'm well into my Senior year, I have my eyes set on Boston as the next destination. I'd love to help out in a music scene that's been apart of my life since High School. I want it to be through Run For Cover, the label that's kept me grounded for all these years.

Noah M. Fisher

+1 (717) 645-1464 // NFISHER@MICA.EDU

SKILLS

Graphic Design (Adobe Suite [Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, Premiere, After Effects]); Web Development (HTML5, CSS, JavaScript); Photography (Analog & Digital); Studio Lighting (Photo & Video); Videography; A/V & Lighting for Theatre; Professional Printing; Layout and Design for Books; 3D Modeling (Sketch Up, Blender)

INTERESTS

Meeting new people; Learning new skills, cultures, etc.; Photography & Videography; Video Games; Archiving; Seinfeld

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Graphic Designer

JAN. 2017 - PRESENT

- Music // Album design & layout commissions
- Web Development // Portfolio sites
- Documentation // Document artist's work

Other Experience

Maryland Institute College of Art, Department of Events -

Performance Space Assistant

Baltimore, MD // OCT. 2017 - PRESENT

- Usher // Be sociable to patrons and represent MICA
- A/V Technician // Ran projection and live sound/music in the various venues across campus
- Theatre Lighting // Rigged and controlled the lights during events
- Woodworking // Built sets for student run plays

Staples - Sales Associate

Enola, PA // JUNE 2015 - FEB. 2016

- Office Supplies // Had to be sociable with customers, learn organization methods
- Easy Tech // Fixed computers, repaired phones and replaced phone screens.

EDUCATION

Maryland Institute College of Art — Photography b/w Graphic Design minor Baltimore, MD // SEPT. 2016 - PRESENT

East Pennsboro Area High School

Enola, PA // SEPT. 2012 - MAY 2016